directorzcut.com 2016-12-25

# Terms

Application Privacy Statement

This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from, you in connection with the associated application (“Application”). The Application is provided by DIRECTORZCUT.COM (and may be provided by DIRECTORZCUT.COM on behalf of a DIRECTORZCUT.COM licensor or partner (“Application Partner”). By using or otherwise accessing the Application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES DIRECTORZCUT.COM COLLECT?

We collect the following types of information from our users:

Personal Information You Provide to Us:  
We may receive and store any information you submit to the Application (or otherwise authorize us to obtain – such as, from (for example) your Facebook account). The types of personal information collected may include your full name, email address, gender, IP address, browser information, username, demographic information, and any other information necessary for us to provide the Application services.

Personal Information Collected Automatically:  
We receive and store certain types of usage related information whenever you interact with Application. For example, DIRECTORZCUT.COM may automatically receive and record information regarding your computer’s IP address, browser information, Facebook user ID, Facebook Page fan status, and URLs accessed. Such information may be shared in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form with our partners.

HOW DOES DIRECTORZCUT.COM USE THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS?

DIRECTORZCUT.COM uses the information described in this Privacy Statement (i) internally, to analyze, develop and improve its products and services, and (ii) as set forth below in the “Will DIRECTORZCUT.COM Share any of the personal information it Collects” section below.

APPLICATION PARTNER TREATMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION.

DIRECTORZCUT.COM may provide personal information to the applicable Application Partner. The Application Partner’s use of your personal information is subject to the Application Partner’s separate privacy policy – and not this Privacy Statement. The Application Partner’s privacy policy is linked to from within the Partner’s Facebook application.

WILL DIRECTORZCUT.COM SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

Personal information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone (with the exception of sharing your information with an applicable Application Partner – see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above). We share your personal information only as described below.

Application Partners: We will share your personal information with an applicable Application Partner (see the “Application Partner Treatment” section above).

Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, DIRECTORZCUT.COM’s agents do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of personal information for the above purposes. Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if DIRECTORZCUT.COM, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that DIRECTORZCUT.COM goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of DIRECTORZCUT.COM may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of DIRECTORZCUT.COM and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of DIRECTORZCUT.COM, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

CONDITIONS OF USE.

If you decide to use or otherwise access the Application, your use/access and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

THIRD PARTY APPLICATIONS/WEBSITES.

The Application may permit you to link to other applications or websites. Such third party applications/websites are not under DIRECTORZCUT.COM’s control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by DIRECTORZCUT.COM of those other applications/websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of such third party application/websites linked to the Application are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and DIRECTORZCUT.COM is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?

DIRECTORZCUT.COM allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change in the event the Application changes.

\- Account and user profile information  
\- User e-mail address, if applicable  
\- Facebook profile information, if applicable  
\- User preferences  
\- Application specific data

CAN CHILDREN USE THE APPLICATION?

Our site and the services available through DIRECTORZCUT.COM are not intended for children under the age of 13. DIRECTORZCUT.COM does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 13 and believes that children of any age should get their parents’ consent before giving out any personal information. We encourage you to participate in your child’s web experience.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT.

DIRECTORZCUT.COM may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Statement when he or she uses or otherwise accesses the Application after such changes have been first posted.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at copyright@directorzcut.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: January 1, 2015

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DirectorZcut collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://directorzcut.com](http://directorzcut.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by DirectorZcut.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information**

DirectorZcut may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To share your information with third parties_  
We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.
  * _\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

 **Sharing your personal information**

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

 **Compliance with children's online privacy protection act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

DirectorZcut has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://connect.directorzcut.com/page/privacy). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Back St, Seekonk, MA 02771  
401-481-9554  
webmaster@directorzcut.com 

This document was last updated on January 13, 2015

**Effective Date:**  This Privacy Policy was last revised on January 13, 2015.

Directorzcut LLC (" **Directorzcut** ," " **we** ," " **our** ," or " **us** ") recognizes the importance of consumer privacy and we take this issue seriously. Accordingly, we have designed this Privacy Policy (this " **Policy** ") in a format that is easy to navigate so that you can better understand our privacy practices with respect to the information provided or collected on or through any of the Directorzcut Services that contain a link to this Policy. The Directorzcut Services are operated by Directorzcut, a company with a mailing address of Back St.,Seekonk Mass, 02771, which is owned by the digital media company Interactive Media Holdings, Inc. (" **IMH** ").

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with this entire Policy prior to providing us with any information through the Directorzcut Services. Throughout the policy we use capitalized defined terms. These terms are intended to have the meaning given to them in the Policy. You should read the entire Policy, but to facilitate your review, [here](https://myspace.com/pages/toschanges#privacypolicysummary) is a partial list of some of the key topics that are discussed in greater detail throughout the Policy.

  * This Policy only applies to your activities on the Directorzcut Services that contain a link to the Policy, and it does not govern activities that are "offline" or unrelated to such Directorzcut Services. We encourage you to review the posted privacy policy on each of our websites and mobile applications prior to using them and providing us with information online.
  * We collect certain information about you when you interact with the Directorzcut Services ( _e.g._ , Usage Information), both by directly asking you to provide us with such information and by automatically collecting it, including through the use of Web Technologies. Some of this information may be shared with third parties, including other Users and Visitors, advertisers, advertising related service providers and IMH affiliates.
  * Third parties – including linked services ( _e.g._ , Twitter), advertisers, and advertising service providers may also collect certain information about you in connection with your use of the Directorzcut Services ( _e.g._ , Usage Information).
  * Your media consumption activities ( _e.g._ , streaming and downloading music, streaming video, IPTV, digital video,  _etc_.) may be tracked through your use of the Directorzcut Services, subject to some limited preference settings. We may retain, use and disclose this media content consumption information as provided below for up to two (2) years from the date in which you consent unless you otherwise withdraw your consent. If we obtain a new consent from you after the date that we obtain your original consent, this period will be extended for additional two (2) year periods each time we obtain a new consent from you. Please review the terms of our [Video Privacy Policy](https://myspace.com/pages/videoprivacy), which supplements this Policy.
  * You may be served with targeted advertising on the Directorzcut Services and on websites, applications, and other platforms owned or controlled by third parties based on information about you collected both on and off the Directorzcut Services, including advertisements based on your location and/or Usage Information.
  * Any information collected about you in connection with your use of the Directorzcut Services may be transferred to the United States. If you are based outside of the U.S., you expressly consent to the processing of your information in accordance with the terms and conditions set forth in this Policy.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us [here](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#11.).

You can also print copies of this Policy by clicking [here](https://new.myspace.com/pages/privacy).

In the event you would like to receive a copy of this Policy by e-mail, please click [here](https://new.myspace.com/legal/privacy/contact).

PRIVACY POLICY

  1. **Who We Are**

Welcome to Directorzcut®, a place where people come to connect, discover, and share. Showcasing artists and their work, Directorzcut gives people access to a massive digital music library. With roots in music and social, the platform is built to empower all artists—from musicians and designers to writers and photographers—helping them connect with audiences, collaborators, and partners to achieve their goals. Through an open design, compelling editorial features, and analytics-based recommendations, Directorzcut fosters a creative community of people who connect around mutual affinity and inspiration for the purpose of shaping, sharing, and discovering what’s next.

Directorzcut services include: (i) those offered on any Directorzcut-branded URL, including [www.Directorzcut.com](https://www.myspace.com/) (the " **Directorzcut Website** "); (ii) Directorzcut messaging services (e.g., instant messaging, private messaging, public and private group chatting, etc.); (iii) Directorzcut music and video services (including, without limitation, any Directorzcut TV-branded video service (" **Directorzcut TV™** ); (iv) Directorzcut developer services; (v) Directorzcut mobile services; (vi) Directorzcut advertising services; and (vii) any other features, content, or applications offered or operated from time to time by Directorzcut in connection with Directorzcut's business, including when Directorzcut is accessed via the internet, mobile device, television or other device (collectively, " **Directorzcut Services** "). This Policy applies to the Directorzcut Services except where a different privacy policy is posted (e.g., the classic service at www.Directorzcut.com and related classic mobile applications), in which case the posted policy applies. The Directorzcut Services are hosted in the United States.

  1. **Scope Of This Policy**

This Policy describes generally how we collect, use, store and share information that we receive from users of Directorzcut Services (" **Users** "). This Policy applies both to individuals using such services that register with Directorzcut and create Directorzcut Accounts and their associated Profile(s) (" **Members** "), as well as individuals who use such Directorzcut Services without registering (" **Visitors** ").

This Policy covers the activities of Directorzcut with respect to the collection, use, storage and disclosure of information through any of the Directorzcut Services that contain a link to this Policy. The activities of third parties or IMH affiliates that provide services (including advertising services) to Directorzcut, or that you link to from us, or that may collect information about you themselves or that we may share your information with, including our affiliates such as Specific Media LLC (" **Specific Media** "), are governed by the respective privacy policies of those third parties or IMH affiliates.

Please note that this Policy does not limit Directorzcut's use or sharing of aggregated, de-identified or other anonymized information that does not constitute Personal Information (as defined below). We may use and/or share such information in any manner not otherwise prohibited by this Policy, without notice or compensation to you, including freely disclosing for any legal purpose non-Personal Information to IMH affiliates, advertisers, partners, content owners, and other third parties.

We will continue to evaluate and update this Policy as we rollout additional services for our Users, employ new technologies and otherwise adapt and improve along with the evolving online and digital world so we recommend that you check for changes regularly. We welcome your comments, as we strive to maintain a Policy that is both transparent and that improves the Directorzcut Services.

To the extent that we provide you notice on any of the Directorzcut Services of different or additional privacy policies or practices  _(e.g._ , at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.

In addition, please review Directorzcut Services' [Terms of Use](https://myspace.com/pages/terms), which governs your use of Directorzcut Services.

  1. **The Information That We Collect**
    1. Information You Provide To Us

**Personal Information And Demographic Information**

We may ask you to provide us with certain information when you interact with the Directorzcut Services. This information can generally be grouped into two main categories - Personal Information and Demographic Information.

Information that identifies you as a particular individual is referred to in this Policy as " **Personal Information**." This would include your full name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. Please note that the term Personal Information does NOT include Directorzcut IDs or Device Identifiers (as such terms are defined below), except to the extent that they are combined with other forms of Personal Information that we have collected directly from you on the Directorzcut Services. The term " **Demographic Information** " refers to information about groups or particular types of individuals that access the Directorzcut Services. Demographic Information does not directly identify you as a specific individual, and would include information such as your age, gender, marital status, income level, and zip code.

We collect Personal Information and Demographic Information through the Directorzcut Services when you choose to provide us with such information, for example, when you register to become a Member. We may also collect Personal Information and/or Demographic Information through a variety of other methods, including when you elect to contact us, submit Profile Content or otherwise interact with the Directorzcut Services.

  * **Registration Information**

Certain features of the Directorzcut Services are only accessible by Members who have registered with Directorzcut and created a Directorzcut account (" **Account** "). In order to do so, you must first complete a registration form that requests certain basic registration information from you, such as your full name, e-mail address, date of birth, and gender (collectively, " **Registration Information** "). Please note that the Registration Information requested by Directorzcut may include both Personal Information and Demographic Information.

  * **Profile Content**

When you sign up as a Member, you are required to create one or more Directorzcut profiles that are associated with your Account (each, a " **Profile** "). Directorzcut may allow you to populate your Profile with certain content chosen by you, and we may also associate additional content with your Profile based on your interactions with the Directorzcut Services, such as your video viewing and other related activities (collectively, " **Profile Content** "). Any Profile Content that Directorzcut allows you to submit must comply with the restrictions set forth in our [Terms of Use](https://myspace.com/pages/terms) at all times. Please note that your Profile Content may contain Registration Information.

The information in your Profile Content is grouped into two main categories – Restricted Information.

" **Restricted Information** " refers to those portions of the Profile Content and Activity Notifications associated with your Profile to which you may elect to restrict access by changing the Profile settings that Directorzcut may make available to you from time-to-time [here](https://myspace.com/settings/profile) (" **Profile Settings** ") or by changing other functionality specific settings on the Directorzcut Services. These Profile Settings may permit you to create a " **Restricted Profile** " by choosing to enable certain (but not absolute) limitations on the availability of certain aspects of your Profile that are not Public Information, certain associated Profile Content, and some of the notifications that Directorzcut produces regarding your activities (" **Activity Notifications** "). Further, unless otherwise provided by Directorzcut, all of your Profile Content and Activity Notifications will still be available to the Profiles that you allow to connect to you. Please note you are currently unable to restrict access to Public Information, which can always be viewed, accessed, and used by anyone with access to the Directorzcut Services, including via third party search engines.

**"Public Information"**  refers to the portion of your Profile Content that can always be viewed, accessed, and used by anyone with access to the Directorzcut Services ( _e.g._ , Directorzcut, other Users, search engines, advertisers, application developers, other third parties, etc.). Any Profile Content that does not otherwise constitute Restricted Information is considered Public Information for the purposes of this Policy. At a minimum, Public Information includes your:

  * Full Name
  * Username
  * Profile URL
  * About Me (the portion of your Profile that provides a place to describe yourself)
  * Profile Photo
  * Profile Cover
  * Stated Location
  * Gender
  * Age
  * Directorzcut IDs

**Public Information also includes:**

  * Any additional Profile Content associated with a " **Public Profile** ," which refers to any Profile for which a User has set the Profile's visibility status to "Public" in his or her Profile Settings, but subject to Mix privacy settings (as further defined);
  * Activity Notifications published on the Directorzcut Services from Public Profiles;
  * Your status as a "Top Fan";
  * Affinity Information ( _e.g._  the relative magnitude of your affinity for Profiles and content); and
  * The number of your connections in and connections out.

You should be aware that the default setting for Profiles of Members who indicate that they are 18 years of age or older is public ( _i.e_  Public Profiles). The default setting for Profiles of Members who indicate that they are under 18 years of age is restricted ( _i.e_  Restricted Profiles), other than for Artist Profiles (as defined in the[Terms of Use](https://myspace.com/pages/terms)) of Members who are under 18 years of age, which are public by default. Other than with respect to Artist Profiles, whose visibility status may not be changed, you may change the visibility status of your Profile from a Public Profile to a Restricted Profile at any time by visiting [Profile Settings](https://myspace.com/settings/profile). Please note, however, that Activity Notifications that were created during the time that your Profile was a Public Profile shall remain public after any change to a Restricted Profile.

Although access to Restricted Information will be limited as set forth above, it is important to note that if you share such information with others, they may copy that information or share it with others, including with the public. Directorzcut is not responsible for the actions of those with whom you choose to share your Restricted Information. For example, you may choose to use the Directorzcut Services to access content pages, which are those pages that, for example, represent an individual item of content such as video or audio, or a collection of content such as audio tracks ( _i.e._ , "Mixes$quot;). When you decide to post content, comments, or other materials to another Member's Profile, a Content Page, or elsewhere on the Directorzcut Services, that information will be disclosed, and available to third parties consistent with the visibility settings for the relevant Profile or content,  **even if those settings are inconsistent with your own Profile Settings**. Content Pages are generally publicly available, which means that posts that you make on those pages will likely be available to anyone. In addition, your video viewing or audio selections may be part of your Profile Content as well as any content pages that you view. Similarly, if you connect to a Public Profile, the fact that you have connected to that Public Profile will be available to anybody with access to the Directorzcut Services.

The Profile Settings that Directorzcut makes available to Members, as well as their functionality, may change as the Directorzcut Services continue to evolve. We will provide reasonable advance notice of the changes in the Profile Settings section, or otherwise. Delays and errors in effecting Profile Setting preferences may occur and we do not represent that they will be immediate, complete, error-free, current, reliable or accurate. If you experience any problems with your Profile Settings, or have any questions or concerns regarding your Profile Settings, or you are interested in obtaining additional information regarding the settings options that may be available to you, please contact us at the [Help Site](https://myspace.com/help).

The Directorzcut Services may allow messaging between Members. More information about who can message whom is available [here](https://help.myspace.com/hc/en-us/articles/202274374-Messaging-on-Myspace-).

More detailed information about Directorzcut's Profile Settings is available [here](https://myspace.com/settings/profile).

**Account ID And Profile ID**

When you create an Account, Directorzcut assigns an " **Account ID** " to identify and organize information relating to your Account and a " **Profile ID** " for each Profile associated with an Account (collectively, your " **Directorzcut IDs** "). The Profile ID may allow Directorzcut to provide a unique internet URL for your Profile (" **Profile URL** "). As described above, Directorzcut IDs and/or Profile URLs constitute Public Information and may therefore be viewed, accessed, and/or used by anyone with access to the Directorzcut Services. You cannot restrict access to Public Information through your Profile Settings.

  1. Information We Collect Or Store As You Access And Use The Directorzcut Services

In addition to the information that you choose to submit to us via the Directorzcut Services, we and our third-party service providers may also collect certain information about you automatically, including through the use of various technologies that passively store or collect certain information whenever you interact with the Directorzcut Services. This may include information about the nature of a User's interactions with the Directorzcut Services, such as his or her media consumption activities (" **Usage Information** "). Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies including [cookies](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTCookie), [web beacons](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTWebBeacons), [embedded scripts](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTEmbeddedScripts), [entity tags](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTETag) and other similar technologies whether now or later devised (collectively " **Web Technologies** "), some of which may be downloaded to the computer or other [Device](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTDevice). The Usage Information that we collect may be non identifying or it may be associated with you, your Account, and your Profile(s). In the event we collect certain information about your interaction with the Directorzcut Services while you are a Visitor, Directorzcut may associate that information with your Account if you subsequently become a Member.

Examples of the Usage Information we may collect include:

  * your IP address or unique [Device Identifiers](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#KTDeviceIdentifier);
  * your Device functionality ( _e.g._ , browser type, operating system, hardware, mobile network information,  _etc_.);
  * the URL that referred you to the Directorzcut Services;
  * the areas within the Directorzcut Services that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences, which artists you are listening to, what videos you are viewing, or Profiles or content pages you choose to connect with,  _etc_.;
  * your Device location (including using GPS and longitude and latitude location information);
  * your Device characteristics;
  * certain other Device data ( _e.g._ , the time of day); and
  * ranking information about you with respect to other Users or content pages that you interact with ( _e.g._ , Directorzcut may record the links to content pages that you post and rank your association with that content compared to other Users).

Please note that certain Web Technologies may set, change, alter, or modify settings or configurations on your Device. Additionally, third parties may use Web Technologies with the Directorzcut Services. We may not control those Web Technologies and we are not responsible for them. For more information on the options that may be available to you for opting out of Web Technologies, see Section 5. You can also avoid the Web Technologies used on the Directorzcut Services by not interacting with the Directorzcut Services and uninstalling any mobile or other applications for which Directorzcut is the application publisher.

More information related to cookies is available in our [Cookie Policy](https://myspace.com/pages/cookiepolicy).

  1. Information We Receive From IMH Affiliates and Third-Parties

Directorzcut may receive various types of information about you from IMH affiliates and from other third parties, including Demographic Information, Personal Information, web usage information, inferences drawn from that data, and unique Device Identifiers.

Directorzcut may also receive or collect certain information about you from third-party websites, platforms, or services in the event you choose to take advantage of various features that may allow you to integrate information on or to the Directorzcut Services. For example, Directorzcut may provide you with the option to voluntarily: (i) sync content from Twitter that will appear on the Directorzcut Services in your activity feed; (ii) authenticate your identity and register for Directorzcut using Facebook's authentication protocol; or (iii) otherwise integrate information from third-party sources. Similarly, we may allow third-party websites, platforms, or services to develop software applications that you can elect to install on your Account in order to provide additional functionality to the Directorzcut Services. These third party integrations and applications are collectively referred to in this Policy as " **Third-Party Linked Services** ". Should you voluntarily choose to take advantage of the Third-Party Linked Services offered through the Directorzcut Services, we may receive certain information about you from the relevant third-party providers, including the following:

  * Name
  * Nickname or username
  * Photo or graphic avatar
  * Unique third-party website identifier ( _e.g._ , Facebook User ID)
  * Biographical or Demographic Information ( _e.g._ , professional title, gender, college attended, etc.)
  * Likes and interests
  * Connections
  * Content accessed or associated with your third party service account ( _e.g._ , articles, songs, videos)
  * Any information that is publicly available on third-party websites
  * Device location (including GPS and longitude and latitude location information)
  * Other information that you choose to share with Directorzcut

We may supplement or otherwise combine the information we collect directly through the Directorzcut Services with information received or collected from IMH affiliates or other third parties.

Directorzcut will treat any information received from third parties (including providers of Third-Party Linked Services) as set forth in this Policy. However, the information practices of third parties are not governed by this Policy. Directorzcut cannot control the treatment of your information by third parties and we are not responsible for their privacy practices, which may differ from those described in this Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of any such third parties prior to choosing to integrate and/or install them on your Account or disclosing information to them. If you have any questions regarding a third party's information practices, you must contact the relevant entity directly.

For additional details regarding how the IMH affiliates collect, use, and share information, please consult IMH affiliates' privacy policies [here](http://specificmedia.com/privacy) and [here](http://vindico.com/legal/#privacy).

  1. Information You Provide About A Third Party

You may have the opportunity to communicate with others from the Directorzcut Services, such as by sending an invitation to a friend. If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, we may ask you to provide us with certain information about the person with whom you wish to communicate (e.g., name, e-mail address, mobile number, etc.). Directorzcut collects such information for the purposes of facilitating the requested communication, which may contain a specific promotional message from you (e.g., an invitation to register for the Directorzcut Services). Unless we explicitly say otherwise, Directorzcut will not use this information for other marketing purposes without first obtaining consent from the person to whom the relevant information pertains. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Directorzcut Services, your e-mail address, mobile number, name or username, and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s). Some of these tools may be third-party tools subject to third-party privacy policies, as further detailed in [Section 3.3](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#3.3.) and [Section 5](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#5.).

  1. **Directorzcut's Use And Disclosure Of Your Information**

Except as otherwise set forth in this Policy, we may use the information that we collect about you through the Directorzcut Services for any purposes not prohibited by applicable laws and regulations, including as follows:

  1. Public Information And Directorzcut ID

Directorzcut may use and share your Public Information, including Directorzcut IDs, for any reason in our discretion. Public Information, including Directorzcut IDs, may be displayed in search results both on the Directorzcut Services and on external search engines ( _i.e._ , those owned or operated by third parties, such as Google).

  1. Restricted Information And Other Information

Directorzcut may also disclose any of your Restricted Information, and any other information we have received from or about you, as set forth in the following subsections. In addition, Directorzcut may use and disclose your information for other purposes when you provide us with prior consent to use your information in such a manner.

  1. Restricted Information And Other Information

We may use any information we collect from and about Users in connection with providing and managing the Directorzcut Services. This may include, among other things: (i) measuring and improving the Directorzcut Services; (ii) facilitating your participation in online games, contests or promotions; (iii) enabling you to communicate and share with other Users; (iv) recommending content or connections (including other Users) to you; (v) analyzing and disclosing your ranking or affinity to certain content or Users to anyone; (vi) providing you with customer support and other requested services; and (vii) responding to your inquiries.

  1. To Third-Party Service Providers To Assist Us In Providing And Managing Directorzcut Services

We may make your information available to our agents and service providers so that they can provide requested services on our behalf. These third parties assist us in providing and managing the Directorzcut Services in a variety of ways, including by: (i) developing or supporting products and features; (ii) supporting our marketing efforts (e.g., conducting e-mail marketing campaigns on our behalf); (iii) processing payments; (iv) administering message boards; (v) fulfilling orders; (vi) processing data or statistics; (vii) hosting media content; (viii) reviewing content for compliance with the [Terms of Use](https://myspace.com/pages/terms); and (ix) assisting with the administration, judging, and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions, and sweepstakes.

  1. To Third Party Linked Services

When you choose to use a Third-Party Linked Service, you are authorizing the Directorzcut Services to share information generated by or available on the Directorzcut Services, including Personal Information, with Third-Party Linked Services, including, but not limited to:

  * Full Name
  * Username
  * Profile URL
  * About Me
  * Profile Photo
  * Profile Cover
  * Unique Directorzcut Identifier ( _e.g._ , Directorzcut IDs)
  * Stated Location
  * Gender
  * Age
  * Biographical or Demographic Information ( _e.g._ , professional title, college attended,  _etc_.)
  * Interests
  * Connections
  * Any Information that Is Publicly Available on the Directorzcut Services
  * Device location (including using GPS and longitude and latitude location information)
  * Other Information that You Choose to Share with Third-Party Linked Services

Your decision to use, link to, install, integrate with or share with, a Third-Party Linked Service when accessing or using the Directorzcut Services is completely voluntary. Directorzcut’s sharing of information with Third-Party Linked Services from the Directorzcut Services is governed by this Policy. Directorzcut is not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices by the Third-Party Linked Service provider, however. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy and terms of service governing the use of the Third-Party Linked Service in order to understand how the Third-Party Linked Service will use the information you authorized Directorzcut to share on your behalf.

  1. Analytics Services

Directorzcut uses third-party analytics providers and products to obtain, compile, and analyze information (that may include your Profile Content (both Public Information and Restricted Information), Demographic Information, Usage Information and/or Device Identifiers about how Users are using and interacting with the Directorzcut Services. Directorzcut may provide such information to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how Users are using and interacting with the Directorzcut Services.

These analytics providers may use their own Web Technologies to provide us with these services and may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, including your Profile Content, Demographic Information, Usage Information and/or Device Identifiers. We are not responsible for those third-party Web Technologies or activities arising out of them. Some third-party analytics providers may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, some of which can be found [here](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#5.). We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out choices.

  1. To Allow Other Users To Find You

Directorzcut uses Public Information and Restricted Information in connection with User search inquiries to establish potential matches to search criteria using tools made available as part of the Directorzcut Services. We make good faith efforts not to display to other Users your Restricted Information except in accordance with your Profile Settings. Please note that Members under the self-reported age of 18 (other than respect to Artist Profiles for artists whose indicated age is under the age of 18 and may appear in people browse results) are not intended to show up in the results of Directorzcut’s “people browse” feature, which allows Users to browse for Members based on certain criteria inputted by the User. Please contact us [here](https://myspace.com/help) if you notice any discrepancy.

  1. To Deliver Relevant Content And Recommendations

To make your experience more interesting or relevant, we may use information you provide, or that we collect about you (e.g., Profile Content, including without limitation page views, queries, media consumption, and connections between your Profile and other Profiles or content pages), and information we may collect from other Users and third parties (e.g., Facebook or Twitter), to assist us in recommending Member and content connections to you on Directorzcut. Directorzcut may also combine your information with information collected by IMH affiliates or others to improve the Directorzcut Services and to make content recommendations to you both on and off of the Directorzcut Services.

  1. To Create A Social Media Consumption Experience

As part of the Directorzcut Services, your Usage Information and Profile Content (including video viewing and audio access) may be shared with other Users. To make your content consumption experience more social and fun, to improve services, to perform analytics, to compare your usage to other Users, to rank your linkages with certain content or Users, and to better make suggestions about other content, we may use any of the information you provide and the information we collect about you and we may share the content of the media that you access on or through the Directorzcut Services with other Users. We may also share your media access through Directorzcut Services (including video viewing and audio content access) as an activity notification by activity notification by, for example, sharing your Profile content (including your full name, username and Profile Picture) on the content page where such video or audio resides. Additionally, your activity may be indicated on your own Profile (in your activity stream or elsewhere) and on your connections' Profile, in each case, both on the Directorzcut Website, and on any other Directorzcut Services, including for example, the Directorzcut mobile App. Other examples of activities that may generate Activity Notifications include, but are not limited to: (i) posting status updates; (ii) commenting on a post; (iii) sharing content or posting on the Directorzcut Services; (iv) sharing content or posting to a Third-Party Linked Service; (v) connecting to a Profile or content ( _e.g._ , a photo, photo album, video, song, etc.); (vi) being tagged in a photo; (vii) commenting on a photo album; (viii) adding a photo to a photo album; (ix) playing a song or watching a video; (x) adding a song to a mix; (xi) updating a Profile; and (xii) adding a cover photo. An example of an actual Activity Notification on the Directorzcut Services is the following: "John Doe listened to the song 'True Love Waits'." Activity Notifications may include Profile Content ( _e.g._ , your full name and Profile photo), and some may aggregate your activity with activity of third parties ( _e.g._ , "John Doe and Sally Smith connected to a photo.").

**Directorzcut makes this feature public to everyone by default, and anyone can see these Activity Notifications**. Note that if your Profile is a Restricted Profile, the Profiles that you have allowed to connect to you will still see your Activity Notifications regarding your content consumption on Directorzcut. From time-to-time we may offer you with options, such as an option to opt out on a session basis, or a persistent basis, from Activity Notifications related to your content consumption. For more information, please visit [here](https://myspace.com/settings/privacy). Session settings are intended to last only as long as your Directorzcut page is open in your browser. If you close your browser, the session-based setting will be reset to public, and your song and video play Activity Notifications will default to the visibility setting associated with your Profile's visibility.  **You should always check the content consumption Activity Notification setting each time you use the Directorzcut Services, so that you are aware of and comfortable with your media consumption appearing as Activity Notifications.**

We may use Usage Information (such as about your media consumption, connections to content pages or Profiles, and posts regarding content pages or Profiles), and your Profile Content, to rank affinity to other Profiles and content. This allows us to identify " **Top Fans** ", and we may use your Public Information to display that you are a Top Fan of an artist, other Profile, or a piece of content. Top Fan status is Public Information – anyone may see your status as a Top Fan. We also may provide analytics tools to Artist Profiles that allow the owners of such Artist Profiles to see Public Information of Users who strongly engage with the Artist Profile or the content pages controlled by the Artist Profile (e.g., videos or songs or such Artist Profile), including Users that are not connected to the Artist Profile.

**Unless otherwise noted, your consumption of media on the Directorzcut Services will be Public Information.**

**To Provide Activity Notifications To Provide Activity Notifications To Provide Activity Notifications**. For additional information on our video sharing practices, please review the terms of the[Video Privacy Policy](https://myspace.com/pages/videoprivacy), which supplement this Policy.

  1. To Contact You

Directorzcut may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to Directorzcut Services or the services or products of Directorzcut's partners to the e-mail address you provided to us in your Registration Information or to the messaging functionality of your Profile(s). By maintaining an Account and/or using Directorzcut Services, you consent to the receipt of promotional materials or notifications to your e-mail address or Profile(s). If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from Directorzcut, you may unsubscribe by changing your [Profile Settings](https://myspace.com/settings/notifications) or following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the relevant e-mail from Directorzcut. Please note that your opt-out request will not apply to subsequent or different subscriptions, or to certain transactional communications relating to your Account or use of the Directorzcut Services (e.g., administrative and service announcements). You may continue to receive transactional messages from Directorzcut even if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing or promotional communications.

For more information, please see [Section 10](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#10.) below titled "Managing Your Information On, And Communications From, Directorzcut."

  1. To Support And Improve The Directorzcut Services and the Services of IMH Affiliates

Many of the Directorzcut Services are free to Users because they are supported by advertising. We strive to make the advertising on the Directorzcut Services as relevant to you as possible. As a result, you may be served ads that are personalized based on, for example, your location, age, gender, content consumption, connections and other information, and we and third parties may use Web Technologies to deliver these ads. Additionally, we may share your Personal Information, Demographic Information, Usage Information, Device Identifiers, and any other information that we receive or collect with third parties (including IMH affiliates and our third-party advertising partners) in order to enable customization of the advertising displayed on the Directorzcut Services, other websites across the internet and other platforms, services and networks, including mobile and other connected Device platforms, and for other purposes not prohibited by this Policy. The parties with whom we may share your information may supplement your information with information they receive about you from others, in order to customize the advertisements they serve. They may also, in turn, share your information with others. If you do not wish for Directorzcut to use or share your information for purposes of personalized advertising, please click [here](https://myspace.com/settings/privacy) to adjust your Directorzcut privacy settings. For additional information regarding the privacy practices of our third-party advertising partners, as well as the choices that they may make available to you, please click [here](https://myspace.com/pages/privacy#5.).

  1. To Deliver Social Advertising To You And Your Friends

Directorzcut and Directorzcut’s ad-technology provider(s), including, for example, any IMH-affiliated company, and third-party providers, may also use Profile Content (both Public Information and Restricted Information) when delivering advertisements to you, your Directorzcut connections, other Users, and other users on any IMH-affiliated company advertising network or third-party advertising networks, including for example, by including your full name, username and/or photo in, or in connection with, sponsored content and advertisements.

If you do not wish for Directorzcut to use or share your information for purposes of personalized advertising, please click [here](https://myspace.com/settings/privacy) to adjust your Directorzcut privacy settings.

  1. To Protect The Rights Of Directorzcut And Our Users, And To Comply With Legal Process

To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Directorzcut may also disclose User information if we believe in good faith that doing so is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect or defend the rights, safety or property of Directorzcut or third parties (including through the enforcement of this Policy, our [Terms of Use](https://myspace.com/pages/terms), and other applicable agreements and policies); or (ii) comply with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas, court orders or consent decrees). To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Directorzcut has complete discretion in electing to make or not make such disclosures, and to contest or not contest requests for such disclosures, all without notice to you. More information is available in our [Law Enforcement Guidelines](https://help.myspace.com/hc/en-us/articles/202248100-Law-Enforcement-).

  1. Business Transfers

Directorzcut may disclose User information in the event we file for bankruptcy, or in connection with certain types of business transactions that result in corporate change. For example, if Directorzcut is or may be (or substantially all of its assets are or may be) acquired by a third party pursuant to an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, liquidation, or similar business transfer, we may disclose and transfer User information to the parties involved in the transaction ( _e.g._ , in connection with due diligence efforts or as a transferred asset).

  1. Co-Branded Areas

Certain areas of the Directorzcut Services may be provided to you in association with third parties (" **Co-Branded Areas** ") such as sponsors, charities and political organizations and will generally require you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of you information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Directorzcut Services, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. We are not responsible for such third party's data collection or practices and you should look to such third-party privacy policies for more information.

  1. Sweepstakes, Contests And Promotions

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (collectively, " **Promotions** ") through the Directorzcut Services that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules, such as on a winners list.

  1. **Choices Regarding Third-Party Tracking And Targeting**

This Policy discloses how Directorzcut collects, uses, discloses, and transfers your information and uses Web Technologies in connection with the Directorzcut Services to which this Policy applies. This Policy does not govern the collection, use, disclosure, or transfer of your information or use of Web Technologies by third parties. The collection, use, disclosure, or transfer of your information or use of Web Technologies by third parties is governed by the applicable third parties' privacy policies. Accordingly, you are encouraged to check those privacy policies for information about their individual privacy practices. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third-party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, some of which are available [here](https://myspace.com/pages/thirdparties).

For additional information on options for opting out of advertising by third parties, you may wish to visit[www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices), or if you are a European user,[www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)

  1. **Information For Members And Visitors Located Outside The United States**

In certain countries, such as those of the European Union, you may have additional rights in respect of the processing of your Personal Information, including the existence of the right of access to and the right to rectify such information. You may also have the right to ask us not to use certain Web Technologies under our control or process certain of your Personal Information (or provide it to third parties to process) for e-mail marketing purposes. While these laws may not apply to Directorzcut Services, we offer certain options to non-US residents:

  * **Web Technologies:**  By using the Directorzcut Services, we are seeking to obtain your consent to the use Web Technologies (other than such technologies that we consider as strictly necessary where we do not require your consent) by providing you with transparent information in our Policy and providing you with the opportu
